Puneeth R

Escalation Specialist - HiPower Support Centre

Bengaluru, Karnataka - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Puneeth-R/bc332220e733906d

To be an asset to my organization by utilizing the recent improving trends and make optimum

use of the available resources for the success of the company. More importantly, working

harmoniously in a team to bring forth the best from self and everyone.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

WORK EXPERIENCE

Escalation Specialist

HiPower Support Centre -

June 2015 to Present

Client: Machine Zone (Supporting 3 Games)

Roles & amp; Responsibilities:

• Escalating tickets to clients, Creating Inquiries regarding the process to receive update

from Clients, Providing feedback to Agents regarding Clients Escalations and internal invalid

Escalations.

Team handling (Mentor)

- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$ Tracking performances of the team members in terms of Production, Quality and CSAT.
- ${}^{\bullet}$ Monitoring Queue, Allocating Agents to different queues, Preparing Reports, Process

improvements initiatives.

- Taking operations training sessions on Gameplay, DSAT reviews, Quality, FTR and Tickets handling.
- Maintaining & ensuring stringent adherence to quality standards, identifying gaps and

opportunities by live assistance. Handled OJT and Tenured Team.

• Handling Supervisor tickets, Lead compensations and Audits.

Sales Associate in Convergys

AT&T -

January 2014 to May 2015

Client: AT&T

Roles & Responsibilities:

- Addressing Customers Billing Inquiries and upselling over Chat.
- Making Calls to customers in case of lead generations.

Process Executive - Operations in Infosys

Cisco -

August 2012 to November 2013

Client: Cisco

https://www.indeed.com/r/Puneeth-R/bc332220e733906d?isid=rex-download&ikw=download-top&co=IN

Contd.,

Roles & Responsibilities:

- \bullet Assisting Clients over Email and Phone regarding Billing discrepancies and Order Management.
- CRM tool experience in Supporting and Reports generation.

Customer Relations Officer in HGS

_

December 2011 to July 2012

Client: MTS

- ${\boldsymbol \cdot}$ Making calls to customers to review customer satisfaction and upselling.
- Handled Escalations from Customers.
- Taking Calls to address Customers Inquiries.

EDUCATION

B.E

PES College of Engineering - Mandya, Karnataka